(Episode 98) The Curtis family is terrible.
One daughter was a substitute bride,
while the other hired a man to kill someone.
And their father
actually has the nerve to spread rumors
that Mr. Bradley likes Noemi everywhere.
He's taking advantage of Mr. Bradley's connections
to make a profit for himself.
Mr. Bradley is unlucky
to have gotten involved with them.
But it would be great if Miss Hall
and Mr. Bradley could be together.
With Miss Hall around,
the Curtis family will not
dare say that Mr. Bradley likes Noemi.
Your information
is out of date.
I heard that
Oliver was arrested two days ago.
From now on, he will no longer
be able to flatter Niko.
How do you know? And who are you?
You seemed to know a lot about the Curtis family.
I thought you knew who I was.
I am Noemi,
Niko's ex-wife.
Oh, you are Noemi?
This wine is quite strong.
What is she doing?
She's not replying to my messages.
What are you doing?